# **SHRIKANT**

**SALES MANAGER** 

# **Key Skills**

• C

#### Certification

Diploma In Labour Law

### Languages

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi
- Gujrati

PHONE I (+91) 9923846622

EMAIL I kansarashri@gmail.com

LOCATION I Pune, INDIA

**EXPERIENCE I** 10 Years 0 Month

# **Profile Summary**

Being a committed team player, want to be a part of a renowned organization, to contribute towards the growth of the Organization, based on my expertise and to further my personal capabilities by learning from the new exposure within the structured framework of the organization. Areas of Strength Include Team Building/Motivation Analysis Recruitment Sales/Business Development Marketing Trainer

## **Work Experience**

#### Sales Manager

Kotak Mahindra Bank

10/2021 - Present

it's overall sales Of all Banking Products, focused on CASA.

### **Branch Business Manager**

**ICICI** Bank

01/2020 - 09/2021

#### Consultant

ISAC Consulting

04/2017 - 01/2020

### **Agency Development Manager**

**HDFC Standard Life Insurance** 

08/2014 - 04/2017

#### **Senior Manager**

Flying India Corporate Services Pvt. Ltd.

12/2013 - 08/2014

### **Project Manager**

Vakrangee Software 10/2012 - 11/2013

Overall Project Operations for Maharashtra State. Project Implementation. Project Completion in Given Time & Budget.

### **Associate Financial Service Manager**

ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company 11/2011 - 10/2012

28 PBs & 8 Retailer giving me a leads to close for life insurance.

#### **MANAGMENT TRAINEE**

LICHFLFSL

07/2010 - 08/2010

I Work with LICHFLFSL 45Days in Swargate & Kalyani Nagar Branch Pune as an Management Trainee for a Implant Training Project, where it was a whole study of financial system, Housing Ioan & clients.

#### Coordinator

**NIIT** 

06/2008 - 10/2009

This was the project for five years under the head 'NIIT at Gov/Private School', i Just have handle the 28 Schools which comes under this project & Aurangabad District.

#### Education

#### MBA/PGDM - Finance

2011

Babasaheb Ambedkar Marathwada University (BAMU), Aurangabad

Grade - 60%

## B.Sc - Computers

2008

Shri Shivaji College, Kannad

Grade - 60%

#### 12th

2003

Maharashtra, English

Grade - < 40%

**10th** 2001

> Maharashtra , Marathi Grade - 65-69.9%

## **Projects**

#### Finacial Inclusion

-735176 Days

Its Prestigious Project of Central Government, which defines that every Indian should have the Financial Benefites which provides by the Government, every Indian should have the Banking Facility.

#### Global Smartfields Summit

153 Days

Global Smartfields Summit aims to capture the current trends in the smart fields market. Smart Oilfields have been in practice for quite sometime now, but the term was coined when service companies began offering digital oilfield solutions as a part of their service portfolio. Smart fields comprises of everything from smart automated wells to every technology that goes into making use of the deluge of data that comes from inside the wells and offshore oil fields less

# Net Banking

89 Days

study of net Banking of its barrier, people awareness, i banking users

# Inventory Managment

92 Days

It was a project on inventory management given by a college